Milind Pawar

Software Engineer at LMS Solutions (India) pvt.ltd. Indore

milind_11pawar@yahoo.in

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Java/J2EE, Maven, C++, Spring, Spring boot, Hibernate, Postgre SQL,mySQL and other tools. Domians like CRM & Medical. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Electronic and Telecommunication. from Rajiv Gandhi Prodyogiki Vishwavidyalaya.

Experience

Software Engineer

December 2013 - Present

Software Engineer.(Java Dev.)

software Engineer at WebPro Technologies August 2013 - November 2013 (4 months)

Education

Rajiv Gandhi Prodyogiki Vishwavidyalaya Bachelor's degree, Electronic and Telecommunication., 2009 - 2013 Little flower higher secondary school Mathematics, 1994 - 2009

Activities and Societies: Science Model Exibitions, football...

Milind Pawar

Software Engineer at LMS Solutions (India) pvt.ltd. Indore

milind_11pawar@yahoo.in



Contact Milind on LinkedIn